<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tany Minds</title><link>/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Tany Minds</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:17:01 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Children can’t get over the parent’s limitations?!</title><link>/en/blog/limiting-beliefs-parenting-children/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 13:45:06 +0600</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/limiting-beliefs-parenting-children/</guid><description>The environment offered to the child is fundamental When parents have certain fears, limiting beliefs, children can’t be otherwise. They get the environment offered by adults, where they extract their information and behavior patterns.</description></item><item><title>Happiness? Don’t look for her because no one lost her…</title><link>/en/blog/about-happiness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/about-happiness/</guid><description>Stop looking for happiness because no one lost it, in any case yours. Maybe someone says he lost his happiness but even in this case it wasn’t his.</description></item><item><title>Economic crisis? What happens to business?</title><link>/en/blog/economic-crisis-business-romania/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/economic-crisis-business-romania/</guid><description>Economic crisis? What happens to business after a month of emergency? The first sight is a total chaos. Companies are turning to online, some know how to do, others not so much.</description></item><item><title>Crisis? – Why are people more afraid, imminent danger or uncertainty of the future?</title><link>/en/blog/crisis-iminent-uncertainity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/crisis-iminent-uncertainity/</guid><description>I would tend to say that people are more afraid of the danger of the present, which is true for part of humanity, those who do not have the habit to think about consequences.</description></item><item><title>When emotions scream at me – About change</title><link>/en/blog/about-change-when-emotions-scream-at-me/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/about-change-when-emotions-scream-at-me/</guid><description>When my heart beats more powerfully, I know I live. When the emotions are screaming at me, I am angry at them too, to temper a little.</description></item><item><title>Where you hit, and where it cracks – What I feel at 37 years old :)</title><link>/en/blog/it-does-not-crack-where-hit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/it-does-not-crack-where-hit/</guid><description>What I feel at 37 years old. I realized how big the number is, only when I wrote it. But I’m not scared. Rather, I feel liberated.</description></item><item><title>Labels, clichés, statistics – Milk will burn? …!</title><link>/en/blog/labels-cliches-statistics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/labels-cliches-statistics/</guid><description>We live with a statistical mindset. We know what will happen in the next moment, we know what the other will say, we know if we are going to hit it or not.</description></item><item><title>Positive Thinking / Personal Development – Why Do We Exaggerate?</title><link>/en/blog/positive-thinking-personal-development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/positive-thinking-personal-development/</guid><description>Why are we exaggerating? Why are we not aware, besides the benefits, of the shortcomings of some tools, skills learned? Are things only in black or white?</description></item><item><title>Does size matter? – Business and creator</title><link>/en/blog/size-matter-business-and-creator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/size-matter-business-and-creator/</guid><description>It all depends on the person interested. As in life, everything is relative and depends on the perception of each individual. For someone the size of a business means how many employees it has, for someone else whose turnover, for others what profit and there are those for whom business value for people matters.</description></item><item><title>Anxiety and business – Free but alone?</title><link>/en/blog/anxiety-and-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/anxiety-and-business/</guid><description>It may seem strange, but these two concepts are closely linked. Entrepreneurship is a perfect amplifier of anxiety. It is the step that, when you do it, you remain free but alone, most often.</description></item><item><title>Do we repeat the patterns with the mistakes? – Vibrating in their own colors</title><link>/en/blog/repeat-patterns-with-mistakes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/repeat-patterns-with-mistakes/</guid><description>Why more people’s trial to do the same thing leads to different results? Even if you follow the steps of some successful people who have already done that.</description></item><item><title>Whistling on the street – in life as in business</title><link>/en/blog/in-life-as-in-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/in-life-as-in-business/</guid><description>“How to …”, “Ten steps to …”, “Five strategies that …”. Okay, but what would be the next step? Maybe ”Why do we want to take the ten steps?</description></item></channel></rss>